{
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "Cactus makes its food in its",
      "answers": [ "Stem", "Leaf", "Root" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "The main source of energy of the earth is the",
      "answers": [ "moon", "star", "Sun" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "Which of the following can make its own food",
      "answers": [ "lion", "cactus", "deer" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "The leafs have tiny pores called",
      "answers": [ "Leaf blade", "Veins", "Stomata" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "Plants store extra food in the form of",
      "answers": [ "Glucose", "Starch", "Proteins" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "The color of chlorophyll is",
      "answers": [ "Green", "Red", "Blue" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "Starch solution on adding a few drops of iodine solution, turns",
      "answers": [ "Green", "BLue-black", "Yellow" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "Boiling the leaf first in the water then in alcohol removes the _______ of the leaf",
      "answers": [ "Stomata", "Chlorophyll", "Leaf Blade" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "Which of the following is a paracitic plant",
      "answers": [ "Dodder", "Cactus", "Croton" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "Leaf Blades helps the leaf to trap the __________",
       "answers": [ "Stomata", "sun light", "Leaf Blade" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 11 ,
      "question": "Leaf makes food in the form of ___________",
       "answers": [ "glucose", "starch", "sugar" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "_________ can not make its own food",
        "answers": [ "dodder", "cactus", "corton" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": "Leaf is attached with the help of the __________",
       "answers": [ "side vein", "leaf blade", "stalk" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "The flattened part of leaf is called ___________",
       "answers": [ "side vein", "leaf blade", "stalk" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "question": "Name the vein that runs throughtout the middle of the leaf _____________",
       "answers": [ "side vein", "main vein", "stalk" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 16,
      "question": "Name of the process by which green plan make their food ____________",
       "answers": [ "Photosynthesis", "Bleaching", "Freazing" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 17,
      "question": "Which solution is used to test the presence of starch in the leaf ___________",
       "answers": [ "sugar solution", "iodine solution", "alcohol" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 18,
      "question": "How do moulds and mushrooms get their food ________________",
       "answers": [ "dead plants and animals", "water", "carbon-di-oxide" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 19,
      "question": "Which part of the leaf helps in breathing ____________",
       "answers": [ "Stomata", "sun light", "Leaf Blade" ], "correct_answer": 1
    }

  ]
}

